<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Passion In Action International]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Passion In Action International]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 20:12:11 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>
The role of Passion In Action International is provide to add value, protect clients and help them achieve their dreams and business objectives.  
 
Mr. Kern will help you innovate and lead with passion. As a sought after consultant, he offers premium quality services, delivered with personal attention, at an affordable price.
 
Passion In Action International cares about empowering business owners, sustainable development and making a difference. Sometimes a coach and trainer helping a business get better, and sometimes we are a matchmaker finding the right partner, investor or distributor. We help companies grow, improve and master change.
 
Your company offers a valuable product or service that clients desire, but perhaps you lack the time or the internal talent to tighten up the business aspects of your operation and achieve the goals desired.  We can provide key insights and identify an effective strategy that will help make your business more profitable and purposeful.
 
Having hands on and actual experience is what works best.  "You can read all the business books, reports, and magazine you want, but it is imperative you have someone who has been there and done that, to guide you down the correct path."  Kern says.  "I've been blessed to create companies, nurture and grow them to the point of others wanting to buy them, and had the option to retire at the age of 44.  I believe my experience and no nonsense approach works and believe my background and track record in business related matters speak volumes.  Retirement isn't for me, I want to help others succeed." 
 
Ron's entrepreneurial spirit drives him to continually discover better ways to address clients' needs, ultimately effecting positive change for them, for their industries and for the world.  Ron doesn't work for anyone nor does he send others to do the consulting, you get his 20+ years of success directly from the source.</p>]]></description>
            <link>undefinedc6de95cb-851f-4689-90a4-31dc14f1661f/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c6de95cb-851f-4689-90a4-31dc14f1661f</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 20:11:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>